(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-29T22:45:31.593719",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
【ご来場のお客様へ】演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください。声出し応援OKです。
[To Visitors] Please be aware of flashing lights. Loud cheering is permitted.
どアニメ宣言！
Extreme Anime Announcement!
アニメにハマって
Got hooked on anime
歌いたくなっちゃった
and felt like singing!
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて…
Singing karaoke while watching my fave scenes...
尊すぎてツラいっ！
is so precious it hurts!
歌いたいアニメ・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Find the anime and game songs you want to sing!
JOYSOUND！
JOYSOUND!
超アニメ宣言！
[Anime Declaration!]
ホロプラス ジャック
[holoplus JACK]
タレントの投稿＆高音質ボイス！
[Talent posts & high-quality voice audio!]
桃鈴ねね 1st Live『開花宣言』 開演までしばらくお待ちください
[Momosuzu Nene 1st Live "Bloom Declaration" - The concert will be starting soon]
ご来場のお客様へ：照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OKです
[Notice to Attendees: Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering loudly is OK]
桃鈴ねね 1st Live『開花宣言』 開演までしばらくお待ちください
[Momosuzu Nene 1st Live "Bloom Declaration" - The concert will be starting soon]
ご来場のお客様へ：照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OKです
[Notice to Attendees: Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering loudly is OK]
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
【ご来場のお客様へ】演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください。声出し応援OKです。
[Notice to Attendees] Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Loud cheering is allowed.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
えっ、えっ、えへん！
Ahem, ahem!
本日は、桃鈴ねね 1st Live『花咲くねねねねねねねね超開花』にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to Momosuzu Nene 1st Live: Hanasaku Nene Nene Nene Nene Nene Nene Nene Nene Chou Kaika!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内をさせていただきます。
To ensure everyone enjoys the live show to the very end, I'd like to share a few guidelines.
お利口だね、みんな～
You're all being such good kids, everyone~
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りしております。
Photography, audio recording, and the use of recording equipment during the performance are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっておりますので、喫煙はご遠慮ください。スパスパ禁止です！
Smoking is strictly prohibited inside the venue, so please refrain from smoking. No puffing away!
そして万が一ご具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせずに近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
And if you happen to feel unwell, please don't push yourself and inform a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージにものを投げ込むなど、他のみんなの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止としております！
Mosh pits, diving, jumping excessively, and throwing objects onto the stage or any behavior that disturbs others is strictly forbidden!
でも、みんなに飛んでほしいところもあるから、そこは飛ぼうね！
But there are parts where I want everyone to jump, so let's jump then!
ルールを守って盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's follow the rules and have a blast!
そして演出の都合上、通路にお荷物を置いたり足をださないようにしてください。これとっても重要です！
Also, due to production reasons, please do not place bags or extend your feet into the aisles. This is super important!
もしかしたら、荷物とか足がなくなっちゃう恐れがあるので、ちゃんと収納しといてください！
Otherwise, your bags or legs might disappear, so please keep them tucked away safely!
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます。
Also, video streaming and photography cameras are present in the venue, so audience members may be captured on camera.
映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please note in advance that video footage and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは #ねね超開花 です！トレンド1位ありがとう！
Also, the hashtag for this concert is #ねね超開花! Thank you for reaching #1 on trending!
まだまだハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてねー！
Keep using the hashtag to hype things up!
それでは、開演までもう少しです！みんなで一緒に盛り上がりましょう！桃鈴ねねでした！
Now then, it's almost time for the show to start! Let's get excited together! This was Momosuzu Nene!
3 2 1 GO!
桃鈴ねね
Momosuzu Nene
満開
Full Bloom
桃鈴ねね 1st Live「ねねねねねねねね！大爆走」
Momosuzu Nene 1st Live: Nene Nene Nene Nene Nene Nene Nene Nene! Daibakusou
ご注文のスーパーアイドル準備中
16:30に到着予定
Preparing your ordered Super Idol
Estimated Arrival: 16:30
準備完了
Preparation Complete
配達中
Out for Delivery
東京ガーデンシアター
Tokyo Garden Theater
な な な な な 「な」じゃなくて
Not "Na na na na na 'Na'"
に に に に に 「に」じゃなくて
Not "Ni ni ni ni ni 'Ni'"
ぬ ぬ ぬ ぬ ぬ 「ぬ」じゃなくて
Not "Nu nu nu nu nu 'Nu'"
の の の の の 「の」じゃなくて……
Not "No no no no no 'No'..."
……「ね」！
...It's "Ne"!
こんねね〜！
Kon-Nene~!
ホロライブ5期生オレンジ担当
Hololive 5th Gen's orange representative,
桃鈴ねねです！
I'm Momosuzu Nene!
異世界から来ましたアイドル志望の新人VTuber
A rookie VTuber aspiring to be an idol who came from another world
まぁ、とにかく明るく行きましょう！
Well, anyway, let's keep things cheerful!
ちょっとくらい緊張したって、滑ったって
Even if I get a bit nervous or mess up,
「うおー！」って感じでさ
with a feeling like "Whoa!",
「どりゃあ！」ってやっていこう
let's go all out like "Yeah!"
あきらめの悪さは長所だよね？
Never giving up is a good trait, right?
ね ねね ね ねね ね ねね ね
Ne Nene Ne Nene Ne Nene Ne
「はぁ〜ん」なこともあるけど
Sometimes things make me sigh "Haa~n",
悔しいこともあるけど大丈夫！
and sometimes I feel frustrated, but it's okay!
今日もしっかり、おめかしして
Dressing up nicely today as well,
いつかはきっと「スーパーねねちー！」
someday for sure, I'll be "Super Nenechi!"
ついてきて
Follow me!
ね ねね ねね ねね
Ne Nene Nene Nene
ねねねねねねねね
Nenenenenenene
ねねねねねね
Nenenenene
ね ねね ねね
Ne Nene Nene
ね ねね ねね ねね
Ne Nene Nene Nene
って、全力でいこう！
Let's go all out!
そんで全開でいこう！
And go full power!
思い切りやれば何とかなるよ
If you give it your all, it'll work out somehow!
ポンコツだっていい
It's okay to be clumsy
誤字ったっていい
It's okay to make typos
ただ駆け抜けていこうよね
Let's just keep sprinting forward, okay?
ね！ね！ね！ね！
Ne! Ne! Ne! Ne!
大爆走
Full speed ahead!
野菜ジュースと炭酸とお菓子、そろえて準備OK！
Vegetable juice, soda, and snacks, all set and ready!
でも朝は苦手
But I'm bad with mornings,
夜も苦手
bad with nights too...
やっぱり睡眠って、大事だよね？
Sleep really is important, right?
ね ねね ね ねね ね ねね ね
Ne Nene Ne Nene Ne Nene Ne
たくさんの人に、愛され合いたい！
I want to share love with lots of people!
ちゅっちゅっちゅ
Chu chu chu
大好きなみんなに、愛され合いたい！
I want to share love with all of you whom I love!
ちゅっちゅっちゅ
Chu chu chu
そしたらなるんだ
Then I'll become
「ハイパーねねちー！」
"Hyper Nenechi!"
やっていって
Keep going!
ね ねね ねね ねね
Ne Nene Nene Nene
ねねねねねねねね
Nenenenenenene
ねねねねねね
Nenenenene
ね ねね ねね
Ne Nene Nene
ね ねね ねね ねね
Ne Nene Nene Nene
って、全力でいこう！
Let's go all out!
そんで全開でいこう！
And go full power!
歌は誰にも負けたくないんだ
I don't want to lose to anyone when it comes to singing!
大きな声を
With a loud voice,
あ、その前に
Ah, before that,
ちょっとトイレ行ってくるね〜
I'm gonna quickly go to the restroom~
もうみんなちゃんと声出してくれないと！
Geez, if you guys don't cheer loud enough,
ねねトイレから帰ってこないんだからね！
Nene won't come back from the restroom, you know!
いくよー！
Here we go!
ねね！せーの！
Nene! Ready, set, go!
な な な な な 「な」じゃなくて
Not "Na na na na na 'Na'"
に に に に に 「に」じゃなくて
Not "Ni ni ni ni ni 'Ni'"
ぬ ぬ ぬ ぬ ぬ 「ぬ」じゃなくて
Not "Nu nu nu nu nu 'Nu'"
の の の の の 「の」じゃなくて……
Not "No no no no no 'No'..."
ただいま〜！
I'm back~!
最後に
Finally!
ね ねね ねね ねね
Ne Nene Nene Nene
ねねねねねねねね
Nenenenenenene
ねねねねねね
Nenenenene
ね ねね ねね
Ne Nene Nene
ね ねね ねね ねね
Ne Nene Nene Nene
って、全力でいこう！
Let's go all out!
そんで全開でいこう！
And go full power!
思い切りやれば何とかなるよ
If you give it your all, it'll work out somehow!
ポンコツだっていい
It's okay to be clumsy
誤字ったっていい
It's okay to make typos
ただ駆け抜けていこうよね
Let's just keep sprinting forward, okay?
ね！ね！ね！ね！
Ne! Ne! Ne! Ne!
大爆走
Full speed ahead!
それでは、次の曲で！
Now then, on to the next song!
ずっとカラカラに乾いているんだ まだまだ夏は終わらない
I've been completely parched this whole time, summer isn't over yet!
みんな、この曲で盛り上がっていくぞ！
Everyone, let me hear you get hyped to this song!
画面に見とれた目で 見上げた放課後
With eyes glued to the screen, looking up after school,
夕暮れにもまだ 青は残ってるかな
I wonder if there's still blue left in the dusk sky.
寝転んだ教科書も 嫌なことも今だけ
The textbooks lying around, all the bad things—just for now,
忘れさせて楽しがなくちゃ
let's forget them all and have fun!
シュワっとあふれた胸が教えてくれる
My heart bubbling over tells me...
僕らはこの夏、超愉快だ！
This summer, we are super joyful!
ずっとカラカラに乾いているんだ まだまだ夏は終わらない
I've been completely parched this whole time, summer isn't over yet!
手足でほら パンパンパン ノッてるから
Look, clap your hands and feet—clap, clap, clap—we're in the groove!
ダラダラうとうともいいけど 体がうずいてもーしょうがない
Lazing around and dozing off is fine, but if my body's itching to move, I can't help it!
じっと何にもやってらんない
I just can't sit still doing nothing!
空気もさぁ
Even the atmosphere...
沈み込んだ表情 沈みかけたあの影も
That gloomy expression, that shadow about to sink...
青いまま過ぎる前になって願ってた
I was wishing before it passed while still blue.
飲み切れなかった日々も 炭酸のせいなら
Even the days I couldn't swallow down, if it's because of the fizz,
これもアクセントって思えた
I could think of it as just a bit of flair.
チラッと見えてた雲も本当は 少しにごっていて
Even the cloud I caught a glimpse of was actually a little hazy,
雨降りのように思い出すんだ
and I recall it like a downpour.
みんなの青春、今日ここで今ねねでいっぱいにしていってください！
Fill up your youth with Nene right here, right now!
大人になればなるほど僕ら 心が動くことも減るのかな
The older we grow, does our heart get moved less and less?
後戻りなんてできやしないから まっすぐ
Since there's no turning back, straight ahead...
僕のドキドキにつられて踊らされて朝起きちゃうような
getting carried away by my pounding heart, dancing and waking up in the morning...
そんな日々にふっと
to days like that, suddenly...
ずっとカラカラのままでいた 僕の音はまだ止まらない
I was completely parched all along, but my sound still won't stop!
イライラくらいパンパンパン はじけさせ 高鳴るほうへ
Pop all that frustration away—pop, pop, pop—towards where excitement swells!
モヤモヤも全部吹き飛ばせ
Blow away all that haze too!
君の思うまま描いていけ
Draw things out just as you wish!
ずっと夜に咲く大輪の花のように 僕ら
Like huge flowers blooming in the night, we...
眩しさを持って咲かせたいの
want to bloom with dazzling brightness!
あてのない言葉が
Aisles of aimless words...
体を追い越すの きっとそれくらいでいいの
overtake my body, and I'm sure that's just fine!
今は何もかも脱ぎ捨てて
For now, cast everything off...
さあ行こう！
Let's go!
というわけで始まりました！
And with that, it has officially begun!
桃鈴ねね 1st Live「ねねねねねねねね☆超愉快！」
Momosuzu Nene 1st Live: 'Nenenenenenenene Super Joyful!'
じゃあまず、ねねの自己紹介をさせていただきたいと思います！
First off, I'd like to do my self-introduction!
ねねが「みんなの心のー」って言ったら、みんな何て返すんだっけ？
When Nene says 'Everyone's heart's...', what do you all reply with again?
その通り！よくできました！
That's right! Very well done!
じゃあ行くよ！ホロライブねぽらぼのねね！みんなの心のー？
Alright, here we go! Hololive Nepolabo's Nene! Everyone's heart's...?
こと、桃鈴ねねでーす！
...wife, Momosuzu Nene here!
もう、待ちに待ちに待ちに待った 1st Live！
Man, the long, long, long-awaited 1st Live!
今回のテーマは、「楽しさ最大出力」をテーマに！ねねがみんなと一緒に超愉快化していくっていうライブにしていきたいと思ってまーす！
With this time's theme being 'Maximum Fun Output', I want to make this a live concert where Nene and everyone become super joyful together!
いいね、いいねー！
Nice, nice!
普通のライブと違って、みんなが参加してめちゃくちゃ楽しめるようにね、いっぱいワクワクとかドキドキを持って来たから、みんな楽しみにしててね！
Unlike regular concerts, I brought tons of excitement and thrills so everyone can participate and have a blast, so look forward to it!
そして、ねねの 1st Album『Peachful Story』みんな聴いてくれたー？
And has everyone listened to Nene's 1st Album 'Peachful Story'?
いいね！もうなんかタオルがちょっと汗ばんでる人がいるくない？
Nice! Aren't there already people whose towels are a bit sweaty?
みんなー！どの曲が好きだったー？せーの！
Everyone! Which song did you like? Ready, set...
おー、うんうん... ちょっと待って、そっちの人、何が好き？
Oh, I see, I see... Wait a sec, people over there, which one did you like?
全部！？全部？こっちの人ー？
All of them!? All of them? How about people over here?
全部！全部か！ねねも全部好きでーす！
All of them! All of them, huh! Nene likes all of them too!
ありがとう！そして今回は...
Thank you! And this time...
ガールズバンドの生演奏でお届けしていきます！ご紹介させてください！
We're bringing this to you with live music by an all-girls band! Please let me introduce them!
キーボードでバンドマスターの、シエリホさん！
On keyboards and bandmaster, Shieriho-san!
そしてギターの、新妻リオンさん！
And on guitar, Niizuma Rion-san!
カッコイイ！
So cool!
そしてベースの、AIMI VADERさん！
And on bass, AIMI VADER-san!
渋くていいね！
So tastefully cool!
ドラムの、坂田菜々子さんでーす！
On drums, Sakata Nanako-san!
はい、そしてちょっとね、配信の方にも触れていきたいと思うんですけど、みんなコメントいっぱいありがとー！
Alright, and next I'd like to talk about the stream too. Everyone, thank you so much for all the comments!
この辺にね、配信の人が見ているカメラがあるの！
Right around here, there's a camera that the streaming viewers are looking through!
イエーイ！
Yay!
みんなありがとー！いっぱいスクショ撮ってねー！
Thank you everyone! Take lots of screenshots, okay!
そして今回のライブの感想とかはね、全部ハッシュタグ...
And for your thoughts on today's live stream, please put them all under the hashtag...
もも... あ、違うな。
Momo... Ah, wait, no.
ハッシュタグ #ねね超開花 でたくさんポストしてくださいー！
Post lots using the hashtag #ねね超開花!
そして今YouTube、そしてTikTokでご覧の方は、次の曲まで聴けるので...
And for those watching on YouTube and TikTok right now, you can listen up to the next song...
まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいなーって人は、概要欄から配信サイトへGO!してくださいー！
So if you want to keep pumping up with us, please head to the streaming site from the description section!
さあみんな、始まる前からギラファねね唱してたけど...
Now everyone, even before we started you were chanting Giraffa Nene, but...
まだまだライブ始まってたった2曲だからね！
The live concert has only just started with two songs!
さっそく次の曲に行こうかなー！
So shall we move right into the next song?!
次は少ししっとりめの曲から聴いてください。
Next, please listen to a slightly more mellow song.
凍えているかな
Is it freezing, I wonder?
桜色に染まった
Dyed in sakura colors,
帰り道の途中
On the way back home,
流れていく春の風吹
The flowing spring flurry of petals.
隣を歩いて
Walking beside you,
少し背伸びしていた
I stretched myself just a little taller.
変わらない距離も
Even this unchanging distance,
本当は縮めたくて
Truth is, I wanted to close it,
言えなくて
Unable to say it,
言わなくて
Without saying it,
「またね」じゃ足りないよ
"See you later" isn't enough.
いつかまた会えるかな
I wonder if we'll meet again someday.
君と何回だって 何回だって 笑い合えた春の日
No matter how many times with you, those spring days we laughed together...
風に舞って消えた
Fluttered in the wind and vanished.
それでも忘れない
Even so, I won't forget.
ほどけた手と手 離れていく
Hands unclasped, drifting apart,
言葉を形にしていた
Giving shape to our words,
甘く触れて溶けた思い
Feelings touched sweetly and melted.
それでも忘れない
Even so, I won't forget.
サヨナラじゃなくて
Not a goodbye,
ありがとう
But a thank you.
言葉を抱いて
Holding these words close,
胸の奥にしまった
Tucked deep inside my heart,
あどけない気持ち
These innocent feelings,
本当は伝えたくて
Truth is, I wanted to tell you,
届けたい...
Wanting to reach you...
届かない...
Unable to reach...
「またね」じゃ足りないけど
Though "See you later" isn't enough,
いつかまた会えるかな
I wonder if we can meet again someday.
君と何回だって 何回だって 見上げた空の色も
No matter how many times with you, even the color of the sky we looked up at...
風に乗って ひらり舞った
Rode the wind and fluttered softly.
かなしみも 思い出も
Sadness, memories,
これから描く 未来地図
and the map of the future we'll draw from here on out,
魔法みたいに 染めて
color them as if by magic.
きっと どこにも 居場所がない
Even if tomorrow comes where I feel
明日だとしても
like I don't belong anywhere...
昨日も 今も 褪せない記憶
Memories from yesterday and now that never fade,
写真みたいに 色付いて
taking color like a photograph...
ずっと ぬくもりを 覚えていた
I always remembered that warmth.
春の匂いがした
It smelled like spring.
君と 何回だって 何回だって
Time and time again with you,
笑い合えた春の日
on those spring days when we laughed together...
風に舞って ふわり 消えた
Dancing in the wind, softly fading away,
それでも 忘れない
but even so, I won't forget.
ほどけた手を 繋ごうとして 離れてく
Trying to hold unraveled hands, only to drift apart,
言葉を探していた
I was searching for the right words.
甘く 触れて 溶けた 思い
Sentiments that melted with a sweet touch,
それでも 忘れない
but even so, I won't forget.
サヨナラじゃなくて
Not a "goodbye,"
ありがとう
but "thank you."
生まれてきたドキドキを響かせていこう
Let's resonate the excitement that was born!
無料パートは終了いたしました。 ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part of the stream has ended. Thank you for watching!